lewrockwell.com 2015-06-30

# Privacy Policy – LewRockwell.com

This site is strongly committed to safeguarding visitor’s privacy. It operates under the following strict privacy policy:

The only information we obtain about our visitors is information we need to process credit card charges and fulfill orders for purchases in the store. The information collected is never revealed, sold, or made public for any reason.

Personally identifiable information provided by visitors (name, email or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business.

**Cookies**

Site visitors receive cookies used during online sessions from third party ad and analytics networks for targeting ad content. Cookies are not personally identifiable, and are not required to visit LewRockwell.com

**External Links**

In order to provide visitors with greater value, some of our pages may provide links to various third party websites. In no case are visitor information or cookies provided to the third party sites.

However, keep in mind that many sites do attempt to capture visitor information when you browse those sites. Once you leave our site, we are not able to alert you should another site attempt to gather information from your browser.

**Security**

We use a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-In**

Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. You can be assured that we never reveal, sell, or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose. This site also gives visitors options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving our communications.

**Other**

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to [contact me](https://www.lewrockwell.com/contact/).
